<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R Creations of Nathaniel Burola</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on R Creations of Nathaniel Burola</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you have some kind of problem with our products? As am hastily invited settled at limited civilly fortune me. Really spring in extent an by. Judge but built gay party world. Of so am he remember although required. Bachelor unpacked be advanced at. Confined in declared marianne is vicinity.
Please feel free to contact us, our customer service center is working for you 24/7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Wrangling and Visualization with Snowshoe Hares/Principal Components Analysis (PCA)</title>
      <link>/blog/1/01/01/hw1knit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/1/01/01/hw1knit/</guid>
      <description>Data wrangling and visualization with snowshoe hares (Lepus americanus)This section of the project concerns data wrangling and data visualization with populations of snowshoe hares (Lepus americanus) in Bonanza Creek, Alaska. The study concerns 5 locales in Tanana Valley in central Alaska from study sites Tok in the east to Clear in the west from 1999-2012 with a time horizon of 13 years.
Attaching all relevant packageslibrary(tidyverse)library(janitor)library(here)library(kableExtra)library(naniar)library(skimr)library(ggfortify)library(tmap)library(ggplot2)library(hrbrthemes)library(qwraps2)library(magrittr)library(factoextra)Reading in the data to form a new dataframesnowshoe &amp;lt;- read_csv(&amp;quot;showshoe_lter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ESM 244: Blogdown Website</title>
      <link>/blog/1/01/01/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/1/01/01/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>