<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on R Creations of Nathaniel Burola</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on R Creations of Nathaniel Burola</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 13:47:08 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chlorophyll Concentrations Along The California Coast in 2016</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/03/04/hw3knit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/03/04/hw3knit/</guid>
      <description>Chlorophyll Concentrations Along The California Coast (2016)This project details chlorophyll concentrations along the California coast, specfically in locations such as Stearns Wharf in Santa Barbara. Concentrations were analyzed with the month, median, maximum, mean, standard deviation, and sample size in mind. The significant difference of harmful algal blooms observed in Cal Poly Pier and Stearns Wharf was calculated using statistical tests such as the F-Test studying an F-distribution under the null hypothesis as well as a two sample T-Test along with Cohen’s D which looks at effect sizes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Wrangling and Visualization with Snowshoe Hares/Principal Components Analysis (PCA)</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/03/04/hw1knit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/03/04/hw1knit/</guid>
      <description>Data wrangling and visualization with snowshoe hares (Lepus americanus)Snowshore hares, otherwise known as Lepus americanus, are a keystone prey species that play an ecologically important role in northern boreal forests and experience population fluctuations of 8-11 years. This capture-recapture study of snowshoe hares was conducted at 5 locales in the Tanana valley from study sites Tok in the east to Clear in the west from 1999-2012 with a time duration of 13 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Map of Hawaiian Land Use, Land Cover, and Watersheds</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/03/04/assignment2part3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/03/04/assignment2part3/</guid>
      <description>Hawaiian Land Use, Land Cover, and WatershedsThis project depicts Hawaiian land use and land cover for all of the main islands in Hawaii. Categories are utilized and displayed on an interactive map such as urban areas, rural areas, forest, sand, rock, etc to show different areas that are covered in different ways. Watershed areas in terms of square mile density are also displayed for all of the main islands in Hawaii.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Data Wrangling, Exploration, and Visualization</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/03/04/assignment2part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/03/04/assignment2part2/</guid>
      <description>Time Series Data Wrangling, Exploration, and VisualizationThis project uses the principles of data wrangling, exploration, and visualization with time series data that concerns the number of adult passage steelhead salmon (Oncorhynchus mykiss) in the Columbia River Basin at Bonneville Dam from the 1st of January to the 31st of December from 1939-2019. The data was collected by the Columbia Basin Research (CBR) research center through the School of Aquatic and Fishery Sciences at the University of Washington under the joint leadership of Research Professor James Anderson and Professor of Biological Statistics John Skalski (Columbia River DART, Columbia Basin Research, University of Washington.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>